

MAGDALENA SZPITALNA

FULL-STACK DEVELOPER

CONTACT

- portfolio: https://magdalenaszpita
 lna-portfolio.netlify.app/
- magdalenaszpitalna@gmail.com
- in https://www.linkedin.com/in/magdalena-szpitalna-/
- https://github.com/MadzikResist
- 665 575 835

EDUCATION

Information and Communications Technology Poznań University of Technology

2019-2023

SKILLS

HTML5 PostgreSQL

CSS MongoDB

JavaScript

React

React Native

Node JS

Express.JS

ABOUT ME

I am 23 years old and I am an IT enthusiast ready for new challenges in the field of programming.

My skills include experience in React and Node.js technologies. I combine acquired programming skills with a creative approach to projects.

I possess flexibility in problem-solving and the ability to quickly grasp new concepts. I am ready to join a team where I can effectively utilize my skills and collaboratively create innovative solutions.

EXPERIENCE

CO-FOUNDER MEETZ

2021 - Present

Creating a mobile application for making friends.

FULL-STACK DEVELOPER CODEALLY

2022-2023

JUDIAII.

Developing software for a platform that hires programmers.

FULL-STACK DEVELOPER INTERNSHIP

2022

Backend and Frontend website development